"lang"
{
	"Language"		"Russian"
	"Tokens"
	{		
		"addon_game_name"						"LET 4 DEF"
		"tip_title"								"This is like normal Dota except..."
		"hints_not_ready"						"Want tips? Check this space again after you have selected your team!"
		"radiant_tip_1"							"You win by killing the enemy Hero once or defending your Ancient for 20 minutes."
		"radiant_tip_2"							"There are 4 of you and only 1 of him. What you lack in levels and gold you can make up in teamplay."
		"radiant_tip_3"							"Enemy creeps give 50% extra gold but zero XP."
		"radiant_tip_4"							"You passively receive 12 XP per second as long as you are alive. That means you will be level 16 in 20 minutes."
		"radiant_tip_5"							"Your enemy commands a lot of creeps but their hit points are capped unless the enemy Hero is close by. The cap increases as time goes by."
		"radiant_tip_6"							"The enemy gets an additional 2000 gold for the first tower they destroy and the bounty is increased by 200 gold for each tower."
		"radiant_tip_7"							"Your side does not have any creeps at all."
		"radiant_tip_8"							"Do not give up if you die a lot in the beginning. All that matters is defending that Ancient."
		"radiant_tip_9"							"You can block the neutral camps to make the enemy army smaller."
		"radiant_tip_10"						"Your respawn time is 4 times faster."
		"radiant_tip_11"						"If you do not pick a Hero in time, you will lose your starting gold."
		"radiant_tip_12"						"Roshan is also part of the enemy army. When he dies, he does not respawn. Try to snatch the items he drops."
		"radiant_tip_13"						"Dire units are extremely easy to kill in the first few minutes of the game. Take advantage of this to get some early gold."
		"radiant_tip_14"						"If your barracks are destroyed, lane creeps will be have full hit points."
		"radiant_tip_15"						"When a Hero uses the Aegis, he receives some of Roshan's passive abilities."
		"dire_tip_1"							"You win by destroying the enemy Ancient before 20 minutes go by. You must not die, not even once."
		"dire_tip_2"							"You can control all the neutral creeps on the map. Unified Unit Orders will make managing them easier."
		"dire_tip_3"							"The hit points of your creeps are capped unless you are close to them. The cap is increased at a rate of 5% per minute."
		"dire_tip_4"							"The first tower you destroy grants you an additional 2000 gold. The bounty is increased by 200 gold for each tower you destroy."
		"dire_tip_5"							"You start the game at level 25 while your enemies start at level 1."
		"dire_tip_6"							"There is only 1 of you and 4 of them. You will die easily if they gank up on you."
		"dire_tip_7"							"Your enemies do not have any creeps at all on their side."
		"dire_tip_8"							"When the enemy kills your creeps they get 50% extra gold but zero XP."
		"dire_tip_9"							"Your enemies' respawn time is 4 times faster."
		"dire_tip_10"							"You can wait for your enemies to pick first before you pick your Hero."
		"dire_tip_11"							"Roshan is on your side unless you attack him. He drops the aegis, a piece of cheese and any other items he is holding. After that he never respawns."
		"dire_tip_12"							"The hit point cap means your creeps (including Roshan) are easy to kill for the first few minutes of the game. Try not to feed them to your enemies."
		"dire_tip_13"							"Your super creeps and mega creeps are not affected by the hit point cap."
		"dire_tip_14"							"When the game begins, your Roshan has very few hit points and the enemies can easily kill him. You can either kill him yourself or protect him."
		"dire_tip_15"							"When a Hero uses the Aegis, he receives Roshan's spell block and armour gain passive abilities."
		"warning"								"Внимание!"
		"difficulty_changed"					"Максимальное время игры и количество пассивно получаемого Силами Света опыта было обновлено в связи с изменением числа игроков."
		"no_dire_player"						"Эта карта требует хотя бы 1 игрока со стороны Сил Тьмы для правильного функционирования."
		"1_player"								"Эта карта не расчитана для игры в одиночку."
		"dota_tooltip_dire_weakness_modifier"	"Очки здоровья ограничены"
		"dota_tooltip_dire_strength_modifier"	"HP cap purge aura"
		"dota_tooltip_xp_aura_modifier"			"Passive XP gain"
		"dota_tooltip_always_deniable"			"Always in deny range"
		"dota_tooltip_yolo_modifier"			"You only live once"
		"objective"								"Objectives:"
		"quest_1"								"Силы Света победят, если продержатся 20 минут."
		"quest_2"								"Силы Света победят, если герой Сил Тьмы умрет."
		"quest_3"								"Силы Тьмы победят, если крепость Сил Света падёт."
		"timer"									"Осталось времени:"
		"custom_npc_dota_roshan"				"Рошан"
		"x_minutes"								"%s2 минут до конца."
		"1_minute"								"Осталось: 1 минута."
		"time_up"								"Время истекло!"
		"roshan_control"						"Roshan is no longer controlled by the Dire!"
		"roshan_control2"						"The Dire has regained control of Roshan!"
		"roshan_killed"							"Roshan has been killed and will not respawn!"
		"new_time"								"новый Осталось времени: %s2 минут"
		"tower_gold"							"Dire received <font color='#CCCC00'>%s2</font> gold for destroying a tower!"
		"autopilot"								"Autopilot"
	}
}