"lang"
{
	"Language"		"English"
	"Tokens"
	{		
		"addon_game_name"						"LET 4 DEF"
		"tip_title"								"This is like normal Dota except..."
		"radiant_tip_1"							"You win by killing the enemy Hero once or defending your Ancient for 20 minutes."
		"radiant_tip_2"							"There are 4 of you and only 1 of him. What you lack in levels and gold you can make up in teamplay."
		"radiant_tip_3"							"Enemy creeps give 50% extra gold but zero XP."
		"radiant_tip_4"							"You passively receive 12 XP per second whether you are alive or dead. That means you will be level 16 in 20 minutes."
		"radiant_tip_5"							"Your enemy commands a lot of creeps but their hit points are capped unless the enemy Hero is close by. The cap increases as time goes by."
		"radiant_tip_6"							"When your towers are destroyed the enemy gets an additional 3000 gold."
		"radiant_tip_7"							"Your side does not have any creeps at all."
		"radiant_tip_8"							"Do not get discouraged if you die a lot in the beginning. All that matters is defending that Ancient."
		"radiant_tip_9"							"You can block the neutral camps to make the enemy army smaller."
		"radiant_tip_10"						"Your respawn time is 4 times faster."
		"radiant_tip_11"						"If you do not pick a Hero in time, you will be forced to play a random one."
		"radiant_tip_12"						"Roshan drops a piece of cheese every time he is killed. Contest Roshan to deny your enemy of additional survivability."
		"radiant_tip_13"						"Dire units are extremely easy to kill in the first few minutes of the game. Take advantage of this to get some early gold."
		"dire_tip_1"							"You win by destroying the enemy Ancient before 20 minutes go by. You must not die, not even once."
		"dire_tip_2"							"You can control all the neutral creeps on the map. Unified Unit Orders will make managing them easier."
		"dire_tip_3"							"The hit points of your creeps are capped unless you are close to them. Creeps spawned later in the game have a higher cap. The cap is increased at a rate of 5% per minute."
		"dire_tip_4"							"Each tower you destroy grants you an additional 3000 gold."
		"dire_tip_5"							"You start the game at level 25 while your enemies start at level 1."
		"dire_tip_6"							"There is only 1 of you and 4 of them. You will die easily if they gank up on you."
		"dire_tip_7"							"Your enemies do not have any creeps at all on their side."
		"dire_tip_8"							"When the enemy kills your creeps they get 50% extra gold but zero XP."
		"dire_tip_9"							"Your enemies' respawn time is 4 times faster."
		"dire_tip_10"							"You can wait for your enemies to pick first before you pick your Hero."
		"dire_tip_11"							"Roshan drops a piece of cheese every time he is killed. Take advantage of that to protect your one and only life."
		"dire_tip_12"							"The hit point cap means your creeps are easy to kill for the first few minutes of the game. Try not to feed them to your enemies."
		"warning"								"Warning!"
		"difficulty_changed"					"Game time limit and Radiant passive XP gain rate have been adjusted to compensate for the current number of players."
		"no_dire_player"						"You need 1 player to play the Dire army for this custom game to work. You cannot play like this at all."
		"1_player"								"This custom game does not offer a singleplayer experience."
		"dota_tooltip_dire_weakness_modifier"	"Hit Points capped"
		"quest_1"								"Radiant wins if they defend for 20 minutes."
		"quest_2"								"Radiant wins if the Dire Hero is killed."
		"quest_3"								"Dire wins if the Radiant Ancient is destroyed."
		"timer"									"Time left:"
	}
}
