"lang"
{
	"Language"		"Russian"
	"Tokens"
	{		
		"addon_game_name"						"LET 4 DEF"
		"tip_title"								"This is like normal Dota except..."
		"radiant_tip_1"							"You win by killing the enemy Hero once or defending your Ancient for 20 minutes."
		"radiant_tip_2"							"There are 4 of you and only 1 of him. What you lack in levels and gold you can make up in teamplay."
		"radiant_tip_3"							"Enemy creeps give 50% extra gold but zero XP."
		"radiant_tip_4"							"You passively receive 12 XP per second whether you are alive or dead. That means you will be level 16 in 20 minutes."
		"radiant_tip_5"							"Your enemy commands a lot of creeps but their hit points are capped unless the enemy Hero is close by. The cap increases as time goes by."
		"radiant_tip_6"							"When your towers are destroyed the enemy gets an additional 3000 gold."
		"radiant_tip_7"							"Your side does not have any creeps at all."
		"radiant_tip_8"							"Do not give up if you die a lot in the beginning. All that matters is defending that Ancient."
		"radiant_tip_9"							"You can block the neutral camps to make the enemy army smaller."
		"radiant_tip_10"						"Your respawn time is 4 times faster."
		"radiant_tip_11"						"If you do not pick a Hero in time, you will be forced to play a random one."
		"radiant_tip_12"						"Roshan is also part of the enemy army. When he dies, he does not respawn. Try to snatch the aegis and cheese he drops."
		"radiant_tip_13"						"Dire units are extremely easy to kill in the first few minutes of the game. Take advantage of this to get some early gold."
		"radiant_tip_14"						"If your barracks are destroyed, lane creeps will be have full hit points."
		"dire_tip_1"							"You win by destroying the enemy Ancient before 20 minutes go by. You must not die, not even once."
		"dire_tip_2"							"You can control all the neutral creeps on the map. Unified Unit Orders will make managing them easier."
		"dire_tip_3"							"The hit points of your creeps are capped unless you are close to them. The cap is increased at a rate of 5% per minute."
		"dire_tip_4"							"Each tower you destroy grants you an additional 3000 gold."
		"dire_tip_5"							"You start the game at level 25 while your enemies start at level 1."
		"dire_tip_6"							"There is only 1 of you and 4 of them. You will die easily if they gank up on you."
		"dire_tip_7"							"Your enemies do not have any creeps at all on their side."
		"dire_tip_8"							"When the enemy kills your creeps they get 50% extra gold but zero XP."
		"dire_tip_9"							"Your enemies' respawn time is 4 times faster."
		"dire_tip_10"							"You can wait for your enemies to pick first before you pick your Hero."
		"dire_tip_11"							"Roshan is on your side but he will turn against you if your Hero gets close to him. He drops the aegis and a piece of cheese when he is killed and never respawns."
		"dire_tip_12"							"The hit point cap means your creeps (including Roshan) are easy to kill for the first few minutes of the game. Try not to feed them to your enemies."
		"dire_tip_13"							"Your super creeps and mega creeps are not affected by the hit point cap."
		"dire_tip_14"							"When the game begins, your Roshan has very few hit points and the enemies can easily kill him. You have to kill him yourself or take him out of the way fast."
		"warning"								"Внимание!"
		"difficulty_changed"					"Максимальное время игры и количество пассивно получаемого Силами Света опыта было обновлено в связи с изменением числа игроков."
		"no_dire_player"						"Эта карта требует хотя бы 1 игрока со стороны Сил Тьмы для правильного функционирования. В противном случае она не будет работать."
		"1_player"								"Эта карта не расчитана для игры в одиночку."
		"dota_tooltip_dire_weakness_modifier"	"Очки здоровья ограничены"
		"quest_1"								"Силы Света победят, если продержатся 20 минут."
		"quest_2"								"Силы Света победят, если герой Сил Тьмы умрет."
		"quest_3"								"Силы Тьмы победят, если крепость Сил Света падёт."
		"timer"									"Осталось времени:"
		"custom_npc_dota_roshan"				"Рошан"
		"x_minutes"								"%s2 minutes remaining."
		"1_minute"								"1 minute remaining."
		"roshan_control"						"Roshan is no longer controlled by the Dire!"
		"roshan_killed"							"Roshan has been killed and will not respawn!"
		"new_time"								"новый Осталось времени: %s2 минут"
		"tower_gold"							"Dire received <font color='#CCCC00'>%s2</font> gold for destroying a tower!"
	}
}